GRAHAM HARRIS

CONTACT

929.244.0668 grahamh1019@gmail Brooklyn NY

EDUCATION

and Italian

New York University, Sept. 2018 – May 2022 GPA: 3.6 Major in Computer Science Minors in Mathematics

LINKS

GitHub LinkedIn Resume Website

SKILLS

- Scrum/Agile
- Project Management
- Data Analysis
- Data Visualization
- Python
- Low/No Code Platforms
- APIs
- Natural Language
 Processing (NLP)
- Large Language
 Models (such as Chat-GPT)

SUMMARY

Technical project manager seeks new role in management or communications. Open to a wide range of positions, including (but not limited to) technical and non-technical management, finance, venture capital, and business/data analysis. Some previous experience in project management, tech development, and seed-stage ventures.

EXPERIENCE

Cloud & Custom Applications Consultant - Capgemini US

June 2022 - Present

Data Analyst:

- Documented client's software requirements across 200+ applications for cloud migration.
- Cleaned and structured data for use in Capgemini's internal data analysis tools.

Scrum Master (Project Manager):

- Facilitated Scrum practices for 2 of client's machine learning team, overseeing a total of 20 developers.
- Achieved 110% velocity measured by Microsoft Azure DevOps Dashboards and queries.

Data Analyst Intern – NYU Entrepreneurial Institute

Sept. 2019 - May 2022

- Analyzed 5 years of aggregate data across 50+ Institute events by creating a behavioral network.
- Organized entrepreneurship events, such as start-up incubators and venture capital pitchfests.
- Delivered weekly 1-hour long presentations on startup resources at NYU.

PROJECTS

Network Analysis (GitHub Link)

- Created 6 behavioral networks from event data for NYU's Entrepreneurial Institute.
- Developed adjacency data and network visualization to demonstrate trends in the data.

Movie Review Sentiment Analysis (GitHub Link)

- Calculated binary classification and logistic regression to determine sentiment for 50,000 IMDb movie reviews.
- Used machine learning tools such as SciKit Learn, Jupyter Notebook, and NLTK to parse reviews and perform analysis.